Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- ISSUES AND ACTIVITIES SERIES, 1920-1986 (bulk 1938-1968)
  - Energy - Reports
    - Legislation, 1973-1974 (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
      [ Save America-Save 25%: U.S. Chamber of Commerce conservation campaign; news clippings; speed limit; Congressional Record-fuel allocation; year-round daylight savings time; voluntary and temporary reduction of energy consumption; energy crisis: position of unions; DOT News; carpooling; Senate Bill S. 2176; Remarks of the President [Nixon] upon announcing creation of the Federal Energy Office; Frank Cawl's files?]
    - OAAA Response to Plan #3, ca. 1979 (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
  - Miscellaneous
    - First Amendment Issues, 1970s-1980s; Safety, 1973 (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
  - Organization
    - OAAA/IOA Merger Plan, 1970 (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
      [Proposed revised constitution and bylaws of OAAA; correspondence]
    - OAAA Regional Representation, 1940s (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
    - Organizational Review Committee, 1969-1971, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box IA2 - Letter Size)
      [Correspondence; constitution with proposed amendments; street map of New York City; list of lease space and price; meeting minutes; organizational and text description of each organization; plan of merger; proposed revision of constitution; minutes; questions; copies of journal advertisement for OAAA; target accounts; dues structure; plans building of government-or notices; meeting minutes]
    - Organizational Review Committee, 1969-1971, Folders 3-5 of 5 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Inc. Organization Memberships, 1932 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
    - Reorganization Plan, 1940, 2 folders (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
    - Reorganization Report, 1946 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
      [Chart of Organization and Responsibilities]
    - Reorganization of OAAA, 1957-1964 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
  - Press Clippings and Reprints
    [See also Box IA18]
    - Clippings
      - Clippings and Copies, 1965 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
        [News and copies regarding War on Ugliness and Highway Beautification; news clipping on billboard control; Lady Bird Johnson; Lyndon B. Johnson; Jack Valenti, White House aide; Administrative Beautification Bill; billboard bonus; scrapbook of articles: Washington Post, Washington Star, Washington Daily News, Wall Street Journal, Chicago, Miscellaneous News Papers]
      - Clippings and Reprints, 1970-1991 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
      - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1949-1985 (Box IA3 - Letter Size)
      - Outdoor Advertising - Magazine Clippings, 1960-1966, 2 folders (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Scrapbook, 1929-1937 [News Clippings] (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Trade publication clippings, 1984-1987 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
    - Publications - General
      - Highway Aesthetics by Richard Hill, 1970 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Member Publications, 1980s, 4 folders (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - More Circulation..., 1939 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Opportunity in National Painted Display Advertising by John Paver, ca. 1952 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Outdoor Advertising Design, 1958 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
        [This copy presented to Odell Hathaway]
      - The Art of Advertising Outdoors by Hal Stebbins, undated (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - The Benefits of Outdoor Advertising by Walter Van Broock, ca. 1930 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - The Big Outdoor, undated (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
    - Publications - Trade Press
      [See also Box IA19]
      - Advertising Age and related papers, 1948-1951 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
        [Reprints, 1948, 1951; Correspondence, 1948-1950]
      - Advertising Agency, 1958 Jan. 17 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Chicago Public Library Book Bulletin, A Trade Association Uses The Public Library, 1953 Jan. (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Outdoor Advertising, undated (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - PR Reporter, 1962 June 25 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Printer's Ink reprints, 1947, 1961, 2 folders (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      - Public Utilities Fortnightly, 1957 Aug. 15 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
  - Public Service
    - Outdoor Advertising contributions to public service campaigns during 1950, 1951 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      [Pamphlet and citation from American Red Cross]
    - Public Service Reports and Correspondence, 1940-1957 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      [Booklet- In the Public Interest; booklet- In the Spirit of Service; reports; correspondence]
    - Papers - Public Service, 1947-1959 (Box IA4 - Letter Size)
      [Organization and history of OAAA; public service campaigns; endorsement of American Heart Association; American Cancer Society; Association of Statistical Records; National Institute for Mental Health Inc.; Association of National Advertisers]
    - Publication, Again We Serve, 1951-1952 (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - Public Service Organizations, 1987-1991, 2 folders (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
      [ Billboard Believers Public Service List; evaluation forms from survey 1989-1991]
    - Public Service Organization letters to Outdoor Companies, [ca. 1954-1991], 2 folders (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
  - Public Service Associations
    - The Advertising Council, Inc., New York, 1942-1965, 2 folders (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - Billboard Believers, 1987-1991, 5 folders (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - Chamber of Commerce of the United States, 1945-1948 (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - Committee on Consumer Relations in Advertising, 1941-1949, 2 folders (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
      [(Note on outside of original folder-To Mr. Blake's knowledge this committee is no longer in existence 1952 Mar. 10); Consumer Movement, Roadside Protection, Public Survey, Business Sponsored Educational Films]
    - Committee on Consumer Relations in Advertising, 1949-1951 (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - Community Action Network, 1991 (Box IA5 - Letter Size)
    - National Committee for Traffic Safety, 1947-1954 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - National Fire Protection Association, 1947 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - National Municipal League, 1947-1954 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - National Safety Council, ca. 1950-1963, 2 folders (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - National Society for Crippled Children and Adults, Inc., 1951-1952 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Public Relations Posters, undated (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Publications: Silent Servant of Public Service Newsletter, 1989-1991 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
  - Public Service Campaigns
    - Armed Forces Recruiting, 1947-1957, 2 folders (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
      [Correspondence; news clippings; articles; photo; letters of appreciation; awards]
    - Conservation, 1956-1984 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Drunk Driving/DECA, ca. 1985 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Education-Papers, 1970-1984 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Foster & Kleiser Files, 1977-1982 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - General Outdoor Advertising Company
      - Philadelphia Local Campaigns, 1953 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
      - Public Service Campaign Brochures, 1953-1957 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Houston Poster Advertising Company
      - Booklet, Privileged Communications, 1963 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Iranian Hostage Crisis-Papers, 1981 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - IRS Public Service Campaign, 1987 (Box IA6 - Letter Size)
    - Letter to Presidential organization chairman about Civil Defense Mobilization, 1967 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous public service campaigns, 1986 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Moral Re-Armament, 1939-1940 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA
      - Publication, Gem of the Month, 1953 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      - Social Welfare Data, 1968-1985 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
        [Clipping, Outdoor Reacts Mildly to New Law on Controls and Beautification; Social Welfare Campaign; correspondence]
      - U.S. Treasury Department of Defense Bond Program, 1951 July (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Patriotism, 1957-1961 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Poster Campaigns- Vietnam War, 1973 Feb. 23 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      [O'Mealia Outdoor Advertising]
    - Radio Free Europe, ca. 1953 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Social Welfare, 1957-1997 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Traffic Safety, 1930-1987, 3 folders (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
  - Sales Associations
    [See also Box IA20]
    - National Restaurant Association, 1950-1951 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Patrick Poster Displays, ca. 1989, 3 folders (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      [Idea Bank]
  - Sales Leasing
    - Leasing, Miscellaneous, 1930-1955 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      [Standard Set Showings of Equal Advertising Value, 1930; Reprints: ASA-Model Sign Ordinance, 1952; Reprints: Wisconsin Operations Clinic, 1952; The System That Charts Itself, 1954 April: Walker & Company; Leases-The Foundation of OA, 1954; Talk by Frank Metzdorf - Successful Leasing Techniques, 1955; a skit in 3 scenes on leasing]
    - Operations Manual Leasing topics, 1939 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
  - Sales Media
    - Media Comparison, 1984-1991, 4 folders
      - Folder 1: Cost-per-Thousand (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 2: Evaluation and Testimonials (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 3: Miscellaneous (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 4: Planning (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising vs. other Media, 1960 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      [Report, The Happy Medium: A Case Study on How to Select Media to Increase Sales]
    - Outdoor Advertising vs. Other Media, ca. 1960, 2 folders (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising vs. Radio, 1939 Mar. 9 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
    - Panels - Junior, 1948-1953 (Box IA7 - Letter Size)
      [Article reprint, Junior Panel Story]
  - Sales Meetings (Box IA8 - Letter Size)
    - Local Sales Session-OAAA, 1965 (Box IA8 - Letter Size)
      [Proceedings of the Local Sales Sessions of the Annual Meeting of the Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Inc.: typed pages bound in hardback cover]
    - National Conference on Local Sales-OAAA, 1962 (Box IA8 - Letter Size)
      (Proceedings of OAAA National conference on Local Sales: typed pages bound in hardback cover)
    - National Sales Session-OAAA, 1963 (Box IA8 - Letter Size)
      [Proceedings of the National Sales Session of the Outdoor Advertising Association of America, Inc.: typed pages bound in hardback cover]
  - Sales Planning (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
    - Industry Information, 1986-1990
      - Folder 1: Structures (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 2a: Miscellaneous (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 2b: Miscellaneous (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 3: Cost Data (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      - Folder 4: IOA Reports (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1959 (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
    - National Sales Volume By Years (Statistics), 1931-1968 (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
  - Sales Planning-- Rates and Allotments (Chronological file)
    - 1958, Junior Poster Panels, Rates, 3 folders (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      [Arranged by state]
    - 1958-1960,Rates and Allotments-OAAA (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
    - 1966, Directory of Outdoor Advertising Companies, 2 folders (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
    - 1966,Outdoor Rate and Market Service: Official Record of the Standardized Poster Medium
      - Book 1, Ala. - Ind., 2 folders (Box IA9 - Letter Size)
      - Book 2, Iowa - Mont., 2 folders (Box IA10 - Letter Size)
      - Book 4, R.I. - Wyo., 2 folders (Box IA10 - Letter Size)
    - 1981 Jan.,The Buyer's Guide to Outdoor Advertising, 3 folders (Box IA10 - Letter Size)
    - 1982 Sept.,The Buyer's Guide to Outdoor Advertising, 3 folders (Box IA10 - Letter Size)
    - 1984 Mar.,The Buyer's Guide to Outdoor Advertising, 3 folders (Box IA11 - Letter Size)
    - 1985 Mar., The Buyer's Guide to Outdoor Advertising, 3 folders (Box IA11 - Letter Size)
    - 1986 April, The Buyer's Guide to Outdoor Advertising, 3 folders (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
  - Sales Promotion (Alphabetical File)
    - Business-Winter, 1941 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      ( F.O.B. Keep Her Buying this Winter, an address delivered at the American Bottlers of Carbonated Beverages Convention by Kerwin Fulton)
    - Local Sales Promotion Plan Subscription Agreement-Sample Forms, undated (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - Merchandising presentation, Libby McNeil and Libby, undated (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Booklets, 1903-1972 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [Booklet, Certification of Incorporation and By-Laws of the Associated Bill Posters and Distributors Protective Company, 1903; Constitution of Associated Bill Posters & Distributors of the United States and Canada, with attached amendments, 1906; booklet, Outdoor Sales Tickler, 1940; booklet, Federal Litigations 1912-1952; booklet, Billboard Basics, ca. 1972]
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1943-1946, 2 folders (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - National Sales Executives International-Organization Handbook and Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - No Waste Words, 1940-1956 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [(Handwritten note, See also To Make a Long Story Short) (long-story-short original painting, record of shipment; radio spot announcements)]
    - OA Ideas, undated (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA-Regions-Promotional Report Number 6, 1940-1961 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA- War Activities Resolution, 1939-1943 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising- The Inside on Outdoor Advertising or How to Lose Business and Alienate Customers, undated (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
    - Papers, 1927-1939 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [ Keeping Pace with the Times and the Crowd with Outdoor Advertising, 1931; hand-labeled with messages Check against Follow the Crowd; Follow the Crowd, flip chart; A Few Facts on Outdoor Advertising, written in response to attack from women's clubs, undated; How Outdoor Advertising Works; Personality of a Salesman-hand labeled; Manual of Information, undated; Manual and Procedure for Fieldmen, 1927]
    - Papers, 1942-1955 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [ Christmas posters; article reprint-Paint Industry; Coffee and Tea Industries magazine; Some Basic Facts; Outdoor Advertising For Banking; 1950-1955 Papers, including sales presentation material for new plant members; application for plant name change; application for poster town membership; statistical data for change of ownership]
    - Papers - Pamphlets, ca. 1951-1961 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [ Speaking of Billboards; Miami, Tell Your Story]
    - Plants-Promotional Ideas, 1935-1952 (Box IA12 - Letter Size)
      [ Messages for Millions: Mass Communication, Land of the Fabulous Boom, Foreman Jock, advertising post cards, Advertise the American Way; El Paso, the year-round outdoor market, etc.; 1 small photograph]
    - Poster Advertising- How to Buy an Audience for Your Advertising, 1963 Feb. 11 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Promoting Financial Institutions, 1940s (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Promotion- Foster & Kleiser IDEA Book, 1970s, 2 folders (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Publication 54 Posters You Can Sell Now, undated (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Reports: The Youth Market,The Poster Showing, Visibility Achieved By Outdoor Advertising, 1950-1983 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Sales Prospectus-Building Supply Trade, ca. 1928 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      [Outdoor advertising for Building Supply Trade with pictures]
    - Sales Tickler, 1929 Dec., 1930 Mar. (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Selling Strategies, undated (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - To Make a Long Story Short, undated (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      [See No Waste Words]
  - Wartime (World War II) Activities
    - Associations
      - Advertising Federation of America, undated (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      - War Advertising Council No-2, 1944-1945 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Campaigns
      - Fire Protection-Outdoor advertising, 1943-1950 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      - Food Fights for Freedom campaign, 1943-1944 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      - National War Fund (Red Cross), 1943-1947 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
    - Committees
      - National Advisory Council, 1943 Feb. 10 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
      - Postwar Planning Board, 1944-1945 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
        [Papers; minutes of Postwar Planning Board 1945 and 1947]
      - Postwar Planning Board Correspondence, 1944 (Box IA13 - Letter Size)
        [ Raymond Loewy Associates Administrative Officers; Fisk, H.E.]
      - War Activities Committee, 1943-1944 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
    - Government
      - War Manpower Commission, 1943-1944 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
        [Campaign of Information for the War Manpower Commission: Poster advertising sponsorship kit]
      - War Manpower Commission; Manpower Requirements, 1941-1947 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
        [Includes Census of Manufactures 1947 from the US Bureau of Census]
    - Newsletters
      - OAAA Information Bulletin, 1943 May-1944 Sept. (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Numbered Bulletins, 1942-1945 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Number 5 on Postwar Planning, 1944 July 20 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - OAAA War Activities, 1943-1945 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - War Activities, 1943-1944, 3 folders (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - War Activities Bulletin, 1944 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - War Activities Flash, 1943-1945 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - War Activities Preview, ca. 1944 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
    - Plant Operations
      - Illumination Procedures, 1941-1942 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
    - Reports and Publications
      - Critical Analysis of Billboard Advertising During World War II, Los Angeles, Calif., 1946 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Essential Characteristics of the War-time function of the Outdoor Medium, 1943 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Guide to Effective War-time Advertising, ca. 1945 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - How Advertising Went To War, 1944 Nov. (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Outdoor Advertising a Channel of Communication, 1942-1945 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Reference to Army and Navy in Advertising, 1941-1946 (Box IA14 - Letter Size)
      - Report: In the Nation's Service, ca. 1945, 5 volumers in 6 folders (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - In the Public Service Supporting Materials, 1943-1946 (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - Miscellaneous Photos, 1940s (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - Press Clippings, 1943-1945 (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - Press Clippings- Posters Work for Victory Congressional Record, 1943 July 5 (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - The Road Ahead, 1943 (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - Report to the Treasury Departments...War Bond Quota Campaign, 1942 Nov. (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - TAB Study of Postwar Activities, 1944 Dec. (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - You Have A Share in Your Town's Post-war Jobs and Profits, 1944-1948 (Box IA15 - Letter Size)
      - Data Units, War Activities, 1943-1944 (Box IA16 - Letter Size)
        [ Hodges, J.C. Files]
      - Record of War Activities, 1942-1945 (Box IA16 - Letter Size)
      - Record of War Activities, Papers, 1949 (Box IA16 - Letter Size)
      - War Related Activities, 1943 (Box IA16 - Letter Size)
        [ J.C. Hodges Files]
  - Building Maintenance and Headquarters (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
    [See also Box IA1]
    - Chicago Building, 1965-1969, 2 folders (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Insurance; maintenance; mortgage; correspondence]
    - Headquarter Task Committee, 1956-1965 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Commerce-Chicago Voice of Business; Business Management; New Office Buildings Chicago 1964-1965; Julien J. Studley, Inc.-Realtor; office layout floor-plan; report on association building; appraisal of property]
  - Energy Crisis
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1973 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
    - Clippings and Press Releases, 1974-1979 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
    - Presidential Press Releases/Energy, 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [ Frank Cawl's Files?]
    - Solar Energy, 1977-1988, 2 folders (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Correspondence; brochure folder by ARCO Solar, Inc.; solar powered billboard; Solarex brochures and booklets; Solarex newsletters-Project Abstracts; biographical sketch of Marshall W. Dietrich-NASA; Department of Transportation booklet-Solar Electricity as a power source for cathode protection]
  - Media Reports
    - Fight Back Posting Campaign, Iran Hostage Crisis, 1980, 2 folders (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Article reprints; press releases; folder-Ayatollah billboard campaign; correspondence; news clippings; first amendment; lists of poster locations; photographs]
  - Organization
    [See also Box IA2]
    - OAAA Organization Set-up, Titles, Responsibilities, ca. 1931-1952 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Charts; outlines; reports]
    - OAAA Regions, ca. 1940-1944 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
      [Maps; correspondence; folder OAAA-Regions-Number 6 (Outline of organized sales promotional effort developed by the local sales promotion committee of the sixth)]
    - Plan of Reorganization of Association, 1932 (Box IA17 - Legal Size)
  - Press Clippings and Reprints (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
    [See also Box IA3]
    - Clippings and Reprints, 1910-1929 (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
      [ The Economic Value of Outdoor Advertising, ca. 1920s; Significant Figures on Cost of Outdoor Advertising per Unit of circulation in United States, 1928; Billboards are Defended as Public Art Galleries, 1922]
    - Clippings and Reprints, 1930-1939 (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
      [Association News, 1924; News clippings- Case Against the Billboard, 1931; News clipping-Boston Herald Award for distinguished leadership by John Donnelly and Sons of Boston, 1938; Facts booklet with cover letter, 1939; Keep America Beautiful report, ca. 1956]
    - Clippings and Reprints, 1940-1955, 2 folders (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
    - Clippings, 1956-1959 (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1962-1964, 2 folders (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
      [(Files of Frank Blake) Billboard ban; forceful removal of billboards by New York Thruway Authority; pros and cons; AAA; booklet-Some Press Comment Favoring Outdoor Advertising]
    - Clippings and Reprints, ca. 1965, 2 folders (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
      [(Question of billboard legality, 1967, billboard compliance, 1965, etc; The Communicator newspaper, 1965; Pennsylvania Outdoor News, 1965; AAA; Highway Beautification Bill-HR 8701-Lady Bird's Bill; night tree cutters; zoning battle; Vietnam support; Lady Bird Johnson; President Lyndon Johnson) (possibly collected by Tocker)]
    - News Clippings, 1965 (Box IA18 - Legal Size)
  - Press - Trade Publications (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
    [See also Box IA4]
    - A Few Facts on Outdoor Advertising, Painted Outdoor Advertising Association, undated (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1948 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
      [Outdoor Primer for basics; Coca Cola; Hamm's Beer; 50th anniversary; Grain Belt Beer; electrical spectaculars; electric curtailment; history of billposting]
    - OAAA News Reprints, 1938-1948 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
    - PAA News (Poster Advertising Association), 1924 June 15 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
    - Spirit of the Poster, undated (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
  - Public Service - General
    - OAAA Public Service Reports and Promotional Booklets, 1940-1959 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
  - Public Service Associations
    [See also Boxes IA5-IA6]
    - Advertising Council, Inc., 1945-1997 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
    - American Heritage Foundation, prefaced by Department of Justice, 1946-1949 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)
      [Freedom train-photo; schedule; flyers; information for press and radio; Boys Town News; meeting with Attorney General of US; speech of Tom C. Clark, attorney general]
    - Partnership for a Drug-Free America, 1990 (Box IA19 - Legal Size)